arizonafoothillsmagazine.com 2010-06-04

# Security and Privacy

We are committed to ensuring that the personal information you share with us remains secure and private. To demonstrate our commitment, we have developed the privacy policy outlined below. If you have any questions about this policy, or the content or practices of our Web site, we encourage you to contact us. 

_Collection of Personal Information and Use_

We only collect personal information when you list a property, place an order, request a service, ask for information or complete a survey. Depending on the service you use, the type and amount of personal information collected will vary. The manner in which we use this data is explained later in this policy. 

However, we may disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or upon any corporate reorganization. Although our site may contain links to other sites, Media That Deelivers, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites. 

_Placing Subscriptions and Orders_

When placing an order, you will be asked to provide your name, billing address, phone number, e-mail address and your credit card number and its expiration date. We use this information only to process, confirm and ship your order. We may also request your birth date, your driver's license number and state of issuance to verify your identity and to complete your order.

 _Using Another Service_

When you request information, submit comment or ask questions via e-mail, we may request your name and e-mail address. We use this information solely to respond to your inquiries, unless you specifically request to be added to our mailing list. 

When you enter an online contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, or e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. Also, as part of a promotion or contest, we may ask you to complete a customer survey to learn more about your shopping preferences. Media That Deelivers, Inc. will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. 

If you request to be on our mailing list, you may receive communications via e-mail or postal mail about our products, services, or contest and promotions that may be of interest to you. Also, from time to time, we may request information from you via e-mail or postal mail. 

You may receive information from us if you participate in a Media That Deelivers, Inc. contest or promotion even if you requested not to be part of our mailing list. If you do not want to receive or share information, please do not participate in these promotions or contests.

 _Disclaimer of Warranty_

Users expressly agree that use of the service is at his or her sole risk. Neither Media That Deelivers, Inc., its affiliates nor any of their respective employees, agents, third-party content providers or licensees, if any, warrant that the service will be uninterrupted or error free: nor do they make any warranty as to the results that may be obtained from use of the service or as to the accuracy, reliability or content of any information, service or merchandise provided through the service.

The disclaimers of liability contained in this section apply to any damages or injury caused by any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, communication line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to, alteration of, or use of record, whether for breach of contract, tortious behavior, negligence or under any other cause of action. 

Media That Deelivers, Inc. neither endorses nor is responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any opinion, advice or statement on the online service. 

Media That Deelivers, Inc. does not endorse, warrant or guarantee any product or service offered by a third party through the service and will not be a party to or in any way monitor any transaction between any user and third-party providers of products or services. As with the purchase of a product or service through any medium or in any environment, each user should use his or her best judgment and exercise caution where appropriate. As with the purchase of a product or service through any medium or in any environment, each user should use his or her best judgment and exercise caution where appropriate. 

Each user specifically acknowledges that in no event will Media That Deelivers, Inc. nor any of their respective employees or agents be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages arising out of (i) the use by such user of any browser owned or operated by any party and/or (ii) the downloading of any software owned or operated by any third party in connection with the service. Each user shall be responsible for obtaining and maintaining all telephone, computer hardware and other equipment needed for access to and use of the Service, and users shall be responsible for all charges related thereto.
